要吃早餐吗
Want some breakfast?
不用了  谢谢
No, I'm good.
我跟你阿姨谈过了
I talked to your aunt.
她说可以
She said it's fine.
房间和其他东西我们都给你准备好了
We got a room for you and everything.
什么时候
When's this happening?
她明晚过来
She'll be here tomorrow night.
太慢了
It's not quick enough.
她要请假一天
She's taking the day off from work
从匹兹堡开车过来
and driving here from Pittsburgh.
最快也就明晚了
That's as soon as she can do it.
有什么事要跟我说吗
Something going on I should know about?
特伊塞尔说我得干一票
Trayzell said I got to do a hit.
什么时候
When?
不知道  他只是让我准备好
I don't know. He said to just be ready.
说我得向他证明自己
I gotta reprove myself to him.
好
Okay.
你以后跟我在一起  我带你去我家
You're staying with me now. I'll take you to my place.
我不是要找地方住
I don't need a place to crash.
我需要彻底离开
I need to get out.
你说你会帮我的
You said you'd do that for me.
我一定会的
And I will.
我相信你
I'm trusting you, man.
迪戈今天回学校吗
Diego going back to school today?
让他休息到周一吧
Let's give him till Monday.
毕竟他经历了那么多事
It's not like he hasn't been through a lot.
是我的线人
It's one of my CIs.
-贾斯敏吗  -对
- Jasmine? - Yeah.
她经常给你打电话啊
She calls a lot.
她是个好线人
She's a good CI.
我想见见她
I want to meet her.
这下可有意思了
Now, there's a fun time.
我妻子跟我的妓女线人见面
My wife and my hooker CI?
我就是想请她来吃个晚饭而已
I just want to, you know, have her over for dinner.
亲爱的  请她来我可能会被炒鱿鱼的
Babe, I could be fired for having her here.
那我们找个普通地方见面
We'll meet her on neutral ground.
跟她一起出去吃晚餐怎么样
We'll take her out for dinner.
不行
Nah.
你有理由不...
Is there a reason you don't--
不让我见她吗  安东尼奥
You don't want me to meet her, Antonio?
亲爱的  你不用在意那些
Baby, there's no need for you
跟我接触的乞丐  瘾君子  还有妓女线人
to feel threatened by the skank, junkie, hooker CI
那只是我工作的一部分
who I deal with because it's part of my job.
那我们就跟她一起吃晚餐吧
Then we will meet her for dinner.
我周五晚有点事
Hey listen, I got this thing on Friday night,
但是可以不去  如果你...
but I can blow it off if you think--
什么事
What kind of thing?
我的订婚宴会
It's my engagement party.
-那怎么不邀请我  -呵呵
- Where's my invite? - Ha.
开什么玩笑  我要跟未婚妻介绍说
Seriously? You know, that's all I need.
亲爱的  这是我的搭档
"Hey, sweetie, this is my partner,
他已婚  但是住在车库里
"The married one who lives in his garage.
不用担心  我们不会那样的
Don't worry, that's not gonna happen to us."
无意冒犯  但我不想让你接近她
No offense, though, I don't want you anywhere near her.
你是说要去约会吗
Does that mean you set a date?
今天是21号  我们在一起半年的纪念日
Ah, today's the 21st, so 6 months today.
天呐  今天都21号了
Oh, man, today's the 21st.
通常20号之后就是21号
Yeah, it usually follows the 20th.
-怎么了  -没什么
- What's up? - Nothing.
这里有两个不相关的案子需要暗中调查
All right, there are two unrelated wire investigations.
根据监控  三个主要地区帮派头目
Surveillance followed three of area central's
到了卡本特名下的这栋房子里
top-ranking gang targets to this house on Carpenter.
缉毒队目前为止还一无所获
Narcotics hasn't gotten anywhere with it,
所以上面想要情报组来负责
so command staff wants intelligence on it.
五分钟后动身
Roll out in five.
我说你干什么呢
Hey, hey, what are ya doing?
我需要张办公桌
I need a desk.
那张不行
Not that one.
那是威尔海特的桌子
That was Willhite's desk.
什么时候可以用了我会告诉大家的
I'll let everybody know when someone can use it.
好
Yeah.
主要监控布置好了
We got the main eye.
现在去北边
We're set up to the north.
明白
10-4.
南边和后巷的一部分都搞定了
We got the south and a partial of the alley.
如果任何人离开那栋房子
If anyone goes mobile from the house,
立即准备抓人
we're in position for a take-away.
老奥和鲁塞克  靠近一点
O and Ruzek, move closer.
看看房子里有没有什么动静
See if there's any movement in the house.
明白
10-4.
等等  有人来了
Hold up. We got company.
这个家伙是谁
Who's this joker?
有枪
Gun!
趴下
Stay down!
-安全  -警察
- Clear! - Police!
-安全  -兜帽男死了
- Clear! - Hoodie's dead.
这个还活着
This one's alive.
C50-21  紧急情况
Charlie 50-21, emergency.
-干什么  -他会失血致死的
- What? - He's gonna bleed out.
我们得好好压住伤口
We gotta put pressure on the wound.
警方开了一枪
One shot fired by the police.
罪犯已制服  现场有便衣警察
Offender down. Plainclothes officers on scene.
这里有发现
In here!
"警察杀手"子弹
Cop killers.
快来看看这个
Hey, look at this.
什么
What do you got?
胰岛素
Insulin.
有人得糖尿病了吗
Somebody was a diabetic?
可能不是
Or not.
这玩意也有黑市买卖吗
Is there a black market for this stuff?
我可没听说过
None that I've heard of.
但是你知道吗
But you know what?
这种盒子刚好可以藏子弹
It's a good place to hide a bullet, though.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
警长
Hey, Sarge.
你有卡尔霍恩县治安官卡片吗
You got a Calhoun County sheriff?
没有  真漂亮啊
No, that's a beauty.
我表妹在跟
Yeah, my cousin's dating a guy
科珀斯克里斯蒂调度部的人约会
that works dispatch in Corpus Christi.
替我谢谢你表妹
Well, you tell your cousin a "Thank you" from me.
那我给你的那张呢
What about the one I gave you?
瓦拉瓦拉那张吗
Walla Walla?
那张我换出去了
Yeah, I traded that one.
-干得漂亮  -谢谢
- Nice work. - Thank you.
我朋友要过来
My friends are coming into town.
我想领他们好好玩玩
I want to give them the grand tour.
我可不想让普拉特毁了我的计划
I'd rather not have Platt deep-sixing it.
你看过咨询师了吗
Did you see a counselor?
咨询师  我不需要看咨询师啊
Counselor? I don't need to see a counselor.
我还不需要穿裤子呢  但我不还是穿着
Well, I don't need to wear pants, but, you know, here I am.
你必须去看
It's compulsory.
好  晚饭我会带吃的
Yeah, and I'll pick up something for dinner.
-大家听着  -不  就这样
- All right. - No, end of discussion.
这是爱德华·雅尔科  已故的街头毒贩子
This is Edward Jelko, the deceased street-level dealer.
这是彼得·托马斯·班菲尔  罪犯
This is Peter Thomas Banfill, the offender,
现在正在县医院昏迷中
currently baking in a coma over at county.
雅尔克应该想的和我们一样
Jelko probably thought like we did
班菲尔得到了批好货
that Banfill was sitting on something big,
所以去他家想敲诈他
went over there to rip him off.
这些是M995穿甲弹
These are M995s,
聚四氟乙烯弹头   可穿透凯夫拉尔纤维
teflon-tipped, kevlar-penetrating rounds.
弹道检查结果显示它和近几起凶杀案都有关联
Ballistics has 'em linked to several recent homicides.
我们在犯罪现场还发现了一大堆这个东西
And we found 100 of these at the scene.
R型糖尿病胰岛素  加拿大的指定药物
It's for type R insulin, which is a Canadian designation.
搞不好我们突袭
And with any luck, our little surprise visit
已经让军火走私贩仓促行动了
got the gun runners scrambling,
也就是说他们会露出马脚的
which means they're gonna make mistakes, okay?
时刻注意着
Eyes open.
艾琳  我们单独说两句
Erin, come here a second, will you?
需要关门吗
Do you want the door closed?
我一直不喜欢开着门说话
Assume I always want it closed.
好吧  硬汉
Okay, tough guy.
贾斯汀提早释放了
Justin's getting early release.
提早到了周五晚上
He's moved up to Friday night.
那很好啊
That's great.
他问我你会不会去
Well, he's asking if you can be there.
如果你不去也没事
It's no big deal if you can't.
你疯了吗  这当然是件大事
Are you crazy? Of course it's a big deal.
他要出来了
He's getting out.
对
Yeah.
怎么了
What?
一大早的表情为什么这么难看
Why do you look like somebody just pissed in your coffee?
出来比进去更难
Gettin' out is always harder than gettin' in.
汉克
Hank.
别这样
Come on.
贾斯汀需要你在他身边  知道吗
Justin's gonna need you around, okay?
什么不露声色深沉的爱  都是扯淡
The tough love thing, it-- it didn't work.
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
告诉安东尼奥我一小时后回来  好吗
Tell Antonio I'll be back in an hour, okay?
好吧
Yeah.
你最近听到道上有人在说
You hear anyone talking about
"警察杀手"子弹吗
Cop-killer bullets out on the street?
没有  我可以打听一下
No. I can ask around.
可以吗
Would you?
就这些
That's it?
要不下次你给我发短信说吧
How about next time, you text me
这样我就不用开一个半小时的车大老远过来了
so I don't have to drive a half hour in traffic?
我想问你想不想一起吃晚餐
I was wondering if you want to grab dinner.
你和我  约会吗
You and me? Like a date?
行还是不行
Yes or no?
什么时候
When?
明晚  七点
Tomorrow night, 7:00.
我已经有约了
I already have a dinner.
取消吧
Cancel it.
除非你赔我400块误工费
Unless you want to pay me 400 bucks for lost wages,
否则我们还是再约吧
I'm gonna have to take a rain check.
我找到胰岛素的来源了
I found the source of the insulin.
多伦多附近的一家"马卡姆医疗用品公司"
A company near Toronto named "Markham Medical Supply,"
他们的销售代表每隔一周的周四都会来
their sales rep makes a run here every other Thursday.
他今早五点离开的
He left at 5:00 this morning.
他们所有的产品都有追踪序号  对吧
I'm guessing they have tracking numbers on all their products?
是的
yep.
那就好  拿到那些追踪序号
All right, get those tracking numbers,
然后追踪定位  然后...
locate him on gp, and--
你已经都做完了吧
you already did that.
对  阿特沃特和伯吉斯已经在去的路上了
Yep, Atwater and Burgess are en route tracking the signal.
干得漂亮
Nice.
帮我个忙  不要做那个
Do me one favor: do not give me
张开手模仿爆炸的手势
one of those open-fingered explosion hands that people do.
我讨厌那一套
I hate that.
如果你要做的话  我情愿击掌
If it's your thing, I'd rather high five.
下不为例
Never again.
等等  霍斯特德
Hey, Halstead.
班菲尔怎么样了
Any word on Banfill?
他还在重症监护室里  你去看咨询师了吗
He's still in the ICU. You seen the counselor yet?
见看了  今天下午看的
Yeah, this afternoon.
我要给所有人发个备忘录
You know, I'm gonna send out a memo
这样大家就不会再问我了
so people can stop asking me.
打住  打住
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
跟谁抱怨呢你
Who do you think you're talking to?
你也就是个新人而已
You got 10 minutes on this job.
因为很多人都问过我了
It's--a lot of people have been asking me.
下次你就这么回答啊
Say that next time.
算了  你说得对  我知道了
No, you're right. You're right. I got it.
那好
Okay.
好的
All right.
博伊特警探
Detective Voight.
事实上  现在是警长了
Actually, it's sergeant now.
你是怎么知道我的
How do you know me?
-卡斯珀  -对  卡斯珀
- Casper. - Oh, yeah, Casper.
他跟着另外一个小头目
He's with the vice lords.
我听说他现在在马里奥联邦监狱里
I heard he's in Marion now.
是  他混得不太好
Yeah, didn't work out too well for him.
不过我看你混得挺好的
I mean, it worked out good for you, though.
我知道你的身份还有你的底细
Look, I know who you are and what you're about.
但你现在洗白了  对吧
But you are legit now, right?
我要跟你单独谈谈
I need to talk to you alone.
不  就在这里说
No, you can speak to me right here.
德安东尼
D'Anthony.
我想让他退出
I want him out.
作为报答  给你张免费出狱卡
Get-out-of-jail-free card for you in return.
原来你想要小德啊
So you want little D, huh?
你想上他吗
You into that?
我来这儿给你难堪了吗
Did I come here disrespecting you?
你知道我投入大量的时间和金钱培养那孩子
You know I put a lot of money and time into that boy, right?
所以我最好给我点票子
See, you may want to give me some paper
而不是什么破名片
as opposed to some damn business card.
给我一万美金  他就是你的了
Give me 10 grand, and he's yours.
会跟你联系的
I'll be in touch.
摩根那个说对了
Yeah, right on Morgan.
对了  你能帮我找辆车吗
Hey, do you think you could hook me up with a car?
我也说不准
Mm, I don't know.
有交货期什么的
There's such thing as lead time, that kind of stuff.
我知道  只是这件事情很重要
I know, it's just kind of a big deal.
那是我的空姐朋友  我有点...
It's my flight attendant friends, and I was kind of--
等等  空姐吗
Hold up, flight attendants?
你从来没说过是空姐啊
You never said nothing about flight attendants.
是  就是那会儿和我同一架飞机的三个姑娘
Yeah, three girls I flew with when I was--
好的好的  我会给你找辆车的
Well, yeah. Well--psh, I'll get you a car.
你应该早说  我会给你找辆好车的
Should of said that upfront. I'll get you a good car.
就是这里了
This is it.
不会有人会往这儿送医疗用品的
Nobody's delivering medical supplies here.
警察  举起手来
Police! Show me your hands!
这肯定就是我们要找的销售代表
This is definitely our sales rep.
乔治·威连科  41岁
George Wilenko, 41.
在马卡姆医疗用品公司工作17年了
He's been with Markham Medical for 17 years.
没有犯罪记录  信誉很好  有通关许可证
No record, fully bonded, has border clearance.
这个人不像个走私贩
This guy's not your typical smuggler.
注意到杯子了吗
You notice the cup?
盖子上有口红印
Lipstick on the lid.
这些就是我们要找的
These are what we're looking for.
C7s  加拿大军方用枪的改造版
C7s, a variant used by the Canadian army.
那里的一家军械厂遭窃
An armory up there was robbed.
丢了3000发子弹和50把C7s
3000 rounds of ammo and 50 C7s were stolen.
在这里  霰弹枪销路更广
Bigger market for sprayers down here.
受害者的妻子当时也在车里
Victim's wife drove down with him.
霍尔斯特德和琳德赛已经去带她了
Halstead and Lindsay are bringing her in.
很好
Good.
你在办51号消防队凯利·西弗莱德的案子吗
You're working that Kelly Severide thing over at Firehouse 51?
是的  停电的时候
Yeah, during the blackout, he got mixed up
他和文斯·基勒那个蠢货打起来了
with that knucklehead Vince Keeler?
我知道基勒  有他准没好事
Yeah, I know Keeler. He's bad news.
我就是这么和西弗莱德说的
Which is exactly what I told Severide
我让他别和那个人搅在一起
and why he needs to stay away from that guy.
西弗莱德的妹妹凯蒂失踪了
Severide's sister Katie was reported missing.
-失踪多久了  -16小时
- How long? - 16 hours.
她是个成年人了  除非失踪满24小时
She's an adult, really nothing we can do
否则我们无能为力  但她是消防员的妹妹
until it's 24, but she is a fireman's sister,
也算得上是我们自己人了
basically one of our own, so area central's
所以上头已经派专案组处理了
already got a task force on it.
他们说如果有需要会通知我们的
They said they'd call if they need us.
所以  我们先做好自己的工作  好吗
So meantime, we got our own case to work, okay?
当然了
Absolutely.
别抓我们哦  警官大人
Don't arrest us, officer.
我的天啊  你们来芝加哥了
Oh, my-- look who made it to Chicago.
你怎么样
Hi. How are you?
天呐  来吧  我带你们参观一下
Oh, my God, come on, I'll give you the grand tour.
-走吧  -我是凯文·阿特沃特
- Yeah, let's go. - Kevin Atwater.
海利  吉纳维芙  薇拉  这是我搭档
Yes, Hailey, Genevieve, Vera, this is my partner.
我一直在照顾她
I look out for her.
那还用说
I'll bet you do.
辣妹啊
Spicy.
-就是这里了  -真棒
- This is it. - It's awesome.
警长您好
Hey, Sarge.
这是什么情况
What's going on here?
女士们  这位是接待警长特鲁迪·普拉特
Ladies, this is our desk sergeant, Trudy Platt.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
这是她的地盘  她处事公正坚决
This is her district, and she runs it firmly but fairly.
没什么事能逃过她的眼睛
Nothing gets by this woman.
跟我来吧
So if you guys will follow me.
你也逃不过
Including you.
我只不过想
I just wanted--
在达菲酒馆有人酗酒妨碍治安
Drunk and disorderly at Duffy's tavern.
达菲酒馆有一半的客人都这样
That's half the clientele at Duffy's.
真不错  你已经缩小了嫌疑人的范围
Well, that's good then, you've narrowed down the list of suspects.
汤米  替我顶一会儿
Hey, Tommy, cover me.
下午好女士们  需要帮忙吗
Good afternoon, ladies. What's up?
你们想要参观一下21区吗
You want a tour of district 21?
乐意为你们服务
I'd be delighted.
阿尔·卡彭  黑帮教父  芝加哥王
你们知道阿尔·卡彭吗
Has anybody here heard of Al Capone?
他来过这里吗
He was here?
名人都来过
Everybody was here.
我们走吧
Let's go.
说实话  医生  你这样问
To be perfectly honest, doc, I'm pretty thrilled
让我很惊慌
with the way that it went down.
让我二选一
You give me a him-or-me choice,
我每次的回答都会是一样的
I'm gonna make it the same way every time.
即使有的事情很公正
People can feel conflicted about something,
人们还是会抵触它
even if it is justified.
我不是这样的人  医生
Well, I'm not, doc.
我不是这样的人
I'm not.
-什么  -我不抵触
- What? - Conflicted.
你还没结婚
You are not married.
那你在谈恋爱吗
Are you in a relationship?
你是在约我吗  医生
Are you asking me out, doc?
我有女朋友
I have a girlfriend.
大概一个月前  我们订的婚
She's my fiancee as of about a month ago.
她对你的遭遇作何感想
How does she feel about what you've been through?
我没告诉她
I haven't told her.
大多数人多多少少
Most of us at one time or another
都会碰到无从解释的时候
meet challenges that we can't explain.
你...
Just--
你是不是想让我感到内疚
Are you trying to make me feel bad?
你是不是就想看我内疚
Is that what you want to hear?
不是这样的
Not at all.
好的  那我可以走了吗
Okay, are we done?
我建议你先别上班了  回去休息吧
I would like for you to take the rest of the shift off.
我妈妈总是管这座城市叫"屠杀之城"
My mother always called it "Murder city."
但是我们第一次来芝加哥时  我就爱上了这里
But the first time we visited, I fell in love with Chicago.
这里的湖  河滨步道
The lake, the river walk.
乔治和我爬上过威利斯大厦的顶部
George and I went to the top of the Willis tower.
天啊  我简直不敢相信
God, I just-- I can't believe it.
为什么有人要杀我丈夫
Why would someone kill my husband?
我们认为他在往国内走私枪支
We think that he was smuggling guns into the country.
乔治吗
George?
他不是因胰岛素而死
He wasn't killed over insulin.
我们觉得他最后一次过来时
And on his last trip here, we think
车里应该装满了这个
his vehicle was filled with these.
我都头晕了  这不可能
I'm hallucinating. This isn't happening.
已经有五个人被这玩意害死了
Five people have already been killed by them.
你不懂  乔治绝不会这样做的
Look, you don't get it. George would never do that ever.
你多久和他一起出行一次
How often did you make the trip down with him?
每隔几个月吧
Every couple of months.
我们一般都住在索菲特酒店
We always stay at the Sofitel.
我要购物  所以他让我先下车了
I shop. That's why he dropped me off.
加拿大没有布鲁明戴尔百货
They don't have Bloomingdale's in Canada.
有情况吗  莫里斯
What do you say, Maurice?
没有
It's all good.
你听说过有人走私枪支进芝加哥的消息吗
You hear anything about lone guns coming in to town?
-哪种枪  -霰弹枪  有很多
- What kind? - Sprayers. A lot of 'em.
加拿大那边有点风声
Heard about something from Canada.
但好像没什么大事
That doesn't make a lot of sense.
快有了
It's starting to.
你有什么消息的话联系我
You hear anything, hit me up.
还有件事
Another thing.
有一个叫特伊塞尔的小崽子
I've been getting some static from this cat
一直找我麻烦
named Trayzell with the Gds.
你知道有谁和他走得近吗
You know anybody got his ear?
和特伊塞尔吗
Trayzell's?
没有
No.
他就是个疯子
He's stone crazy.
他不会听任何人的话
He don't listen to nobody.
对了  我跟你说件事
And I need to bring you in on something.
州检察官要找人起诉我
State's attorney's getting someone to flip on me,
可能要立案还是怎样
buildin' a case or somethin'.
我一点风声都没听到
I haven't got wind of anything.
现在你听到了
Now you have.
五千块
Five stacks.
告诉我是谁  再给你加钱
More when you get me that name.
知道了
I got you.
博伊特  讲
Go for Voight.
我们找到了点东西
We got somethin'.
同样的子弹
These are our bullets.
你们知道这玩意儿速度有多快吗
Can you believe the velocity of these things?
法医发现有一发子弹穿过电视
Forensics traced one round that went through the TV,
穿墙而过  最后卡在
through the wall, ended up halfway
街对面停着的一辆
through the engine block of an ice cream truck
冰淇淋车的发动机里
parked across the street.
现在总共七起谋杀案了
Seven homicides and counting.
那个寡妇在说谎
Our widow's lying.
她的手机供应商说她从未去过布鲁明戴尔百货
Her cell phone provider said she was never at Bloomingdale's.
她一下午都待在滨水市
She spent the afternoon up in Edgewater.
你最好实话实说
We're gonna get real honest real quick.
你认识这些人吗
Do you recognize these men?
-天呐  -是啊  我们也认不出了
- Oh, God. - Yeah, neither can we.
他的脸被子弹打得血肉模糊
His face was shot off by the bullets
就是你和你丈夫带进芝加哥的那些子弹
you and your husband brought into Chicago.
你们为什么这么对我
Why are you doing this?
你对我们说谎了
You lied to us.
你没去布鲁明戴尔百货  而是在滨水市
You weren't browsing Bloomingdale's. You were in Edgewater.
你们肯定赚了不少吧
You and your husband had a nice run, right?
一开始贩卖点大麻之类的
You start off with something simple like x or kush,
接着就贪得无厌  发展到军火走私
and you got greedy, and you upgraded to gun-running.
结果害乔治被杀  而你成了帮凶
You got George killed, which makes you an accessory to his murder.
再给你一次机会吧  坦白从宽
So we're gonna try this again, only this time the truth.
我是去见朋友
I was visiting a friend.
前男友
An ex-boyfriend.
要说谎也编得靠谱点啊
If you're gonna lie, put some effort into it for me.
打电话问他  他会说的
Call him. He'll tell you.
把名字和号码写下来
Name, number.
你要告诉我你那天做的一切
I want you to take me through your entire day,
去过哪里  和谁说过话
every stop you made, every person you talked to,
都做过什么
everything you did.
我已经告诉过你了
I already told you.
那就再说一遍
Tell me again.
我们凌晨4点30分出发
We were on the road by 4:30.
过了安阿伯市越过边境线才停下来
Didn't stop till we crossed the border just past Ann Arbor.
喝了点咖啡  加了点油  上了个厕所
Got some coffee, some gas. Used the washroom.
乔治接了一个侄子打来的电话
George got a phone call from our nephew--
-侄子是谁  -他就住在芝加哥
- Who's the nephew? - He lives here.
他想见见乔治
He likes to meet up with George--
天呐  不会是小迈的
Oh, God, Mikey doesn't know.
小迈姓什么
Does Mikey have a last name?
迈克尔·甘茨  住在加菲尔德公园东区
Michael Ganz, lives in east Garfield Park,
有持枪抢劫犯罪记录  手下有一小伙人
has a record: robbery, possession. Runs with a small crew.
在巴克斯发现了
Claire's ex-boyfriend checks out
克莱尔的前男友
right down to the 500 Bucks.
查到甘茨的手机了
Got a ping on Ganz's phone,
我调出了他24小时内所打出的电话
pulled all the numbers he's called in the last 24 hours.
本周最佳员工啊  吉恩  非你莫属
Employee of the week, Jin, right here.
他一直在打同一个号码
All the calls were to the same numbers,
用那个号码的手机是在盖奇公园
a cell phone registered to a Lucky M Pawn and Loan
-幸运M典当行名下的  -幸运M
- in Gage Park. - Lucky M.
我认识那里的家伙
I know that ding-dong.
我们去问问他  走吧
We'll go talk to him. Come on.
-老奥  -怎么了
- Hey, O. - Yeah.
回来找我  我有活要你干
I'm gonna need you later off the books.
行
Yeah.
-走吧  -走
- Let's go. - Come on.
米尔纳先生
Mr. Milner.
埃尔文
Alvin.
高利贷生意还好吧
Hey. So how's the usury business?
我不干那档子事
I don't run that kind of operation.
那就好
Good for you.
那么  加拿大来的枪呢
So, um, guns coming in from Canada.
我只是个中介
I just introduce people.
这话什么意思
Wha--wha-- what does that mean?
没什么  就那么一说而已  懂吗
Nothin'. I'm just telling you, you know?
我不懂
No, I don't know.
我不知道什么加拿大枪
I don't know anything about Canadian guns.
那你干嘛说自己是中介
Then why did you say, "I just introduce people"?
很奇怪啊
It just seems odd.
你让我紧张了
You make me nervous.
为什么
Why? Huh?
-要原因吗  -对
- Why? - Yeah.
要我提上次你来我店里的事吗
How about the last time you were in my shop, huh?
你把一瓶饮料倒进了我的珠宝盒
You took a Nine Iron to my jewelry case.
-是在这里吗  -埃尔文
- That was here? - Alvin.
我什么都不知道  好吗
I don't know anything, okay?
让我  让我看看那个
Let me, uh-- let me see that.
就那个  那个东西
Right there, right there. Right--right over there, yeah.
他和甘茨约好明天下午两点交易
He set up a buy with Ganz tomorrow, 2:00 P.M.
丹尼
Hey, Danny.
你来了  杰
Hi, Jay.
给你的熏牛肉
Pastrami for Danny,
给你的烤火鸡
and smoked turkey for you.
好重啊
Oh, gosh.
可以一直吃到感恩节啦
We're going to be eating this till Thanksgiving.
我去给你拿个三明治
Hey, let me get you a sandwich.
不用了  我得走了
No, I can't. I gotta run.
至少吃块蛋糕再走吧
Oh, well, let me at least give you a slice of cake to go.
他每次都不好受
This is always a tough day for him.
他不会吃的
He won't eat it.
最后每次都丢掉
I just end up throwing it out.
那就给我一小块吧
Small slice.
能给我看看你的驾照吗
Can I see your driver's license?
-霍斯特德  情报局  -这是骚扰
- Halstead. Intelligence. - This is harassment.
只是吃点生日蛋糕而已
Just eating some birthday cake.
今天是某人生日啊
Today would have been a birthday.
快逮捕他
Arrest him.
-把他赶走  -抱歉  伙计
- Get him out of here! - Sorry, pal.
两个混蛋狼狈为奸是吗
All you dirty bastards stick together.
你们就是这样
You always have.
朗尼  七年前的今天
Seven years ago today, Lonnie.
就今天
Today.
-给我滚  -整整七年
- Get outta here! - Seven years!
否则他现在都该15岁了
He would have been 15!
我要叫我的律师了  我要申请遏制令
I'm gonna call my lawyer. I'm getting a restraining order.
放心  你迟早会需要的
I'm gonna give you a reason to need one one day.
天呐
Oh, God.
给你和你的变态儿子用
You and your sick-ass son.
没查到和枪有关的任何信息
Okay. I got nothin' on the guns.
抱歉
Sorry.
就这样
That's it?
下次发条短信给我就行了
Next time, text me.
还有  我明天的约会取消了
And also, my date canceled for tomorrow,
那就赴你的约吧
so you're on.
你想看我穿什么
What do you want me to wear?
穿保守点
Dress conservative.
重复一遍
Repeat that back to me.
我会穿得很保守
I will dress conservative.
七点  "爱情你好"餐厅
Ciao Amore at 7:00.
好吧
Okay.
到时候见
See you then.
西弗莱德
Severide.
我不知道该去哪儿
I didn't know where else to go,
我  我不...
and, um, and I don't--
大家一点消息都没有
No one's heard anything.
我不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what to do.
我们会找到她的  好吗
Hey, we're gonna find her, okay?
-我知道  -我保证
- Yeah. - I promise.
一批很优秀的警员在查这事
We've got really good guys on this.
我知道这很可怕  你妹妹独自一人
And I know it's scary, and I know your sister's alone,
但我们会找到她的
but we're gonna find her.
来吧
Come on.
你好啊  特伊塞尔
Hey, Trayzell.
兄弟
Bro.
我亲自去找你想跟你合作
I came to you man to man, tried to do business.
结果你跟我谈条件
You want to negotiate?
可能卡斯珀进监狱前没跟你说过
Maybe Casper didn't tell you before he got sent up,
不过  我可不喜欢谈条件
but... I don't like negotiating.
可能他没说过  我的橄榄枝向来只伸出一次
Maybe he didn't tell you, I make offers once.
把他手铐打开吧
You can uncuff him.
看着我
Look at me.
德安东尼必须退伙
D'Anthony is out
就从现在开始
as of this minute.
你要敢打他主意
You look sideways at him,
下次再被带走就你别想回去了
you're goin' on a ride you're never coming back from.
听懂了吗
You understand?
那就好
All right.
我们走
Let's get outta here.
大家要注意安全
Let's keep our heads down.
就当迈克手里有重型武器
Assume Mike is packing heavy stuff.
-你好啊  -看看你
- Hey. - Look at you,
神清气爽啊
all fresh like a daisy.
是啊  撸一管真有效
Yeah, what a wank.
听着  我放倒的那个人有消息了吗
Hey, listen, any word on the guy I dropped?
-没有  还在重症监护室里  -好吧
- Nah, still in the ICU. - All right.
你的咨询师怎么说
Hey, what'd your counselor say?
说我对精神创伤应对得很好
Oh, that I'm coping well with the trauma,
但我觉得她是指和你一起工作
but I think she was talking about working with you.
你留在车里
You're in the van.
等等  为什么不让我和你去交易
Wait, why can't I do the buy with you?
因为安东尼奥抢在你前面说了
'Cause Antonio called shotgun before you did.
你在开玩...
You gotta be--
埃尔  这样子还得多久  我没事好吗
Al, how long is this gonna go on for? I'm fine.
-"圣诞节"  -什么
- Christmas. - What?
我们的行动暗号是"圣诞节"
Christmas is the takedown word.
我在卡迈恩餐厅定了位置庆祝他出狱
Reservation's all set at Carmine's for when he's out.
他们把包间留给我们了
They gave us the back room,
所以你都想请谁
so who do you want me to invite?
不用大张旗鼓  就我们三个就行
Oh, let's keep it small, just the three of us.
-真的吗  -我觉得
- Yeah? - I don't think
他现在不该跟那些狐朋狗友混在一起
he should be around his old friends just yet.
好吧
Okay.
就是他  甘茨
That's our boy, Ganz.
米尔纳说你们想弄点装备是么
Milner says you're huntin' for hardware?
如果真如他说的那样货真价实
If they're the quality Milner said they are,
我们要的可不少
we'll take most of 'em off your hands.
我带你们去看
I'll take you to it.
-上车吧  -得了吧
- Get in. - Aw, come on.
只许带着钱的那个上来
Only one of you with the money.
算了
Forget it.
我无所谓
Fine with me.
等等  等等  等会儿
Hey, hey--whoa, whoa, whoa, wait--wait a sec.
等会儿
Wait--wait--wait a sec.
-好的  -不行
- Okay. - No.
没问题
All right.
他就是个怂货
He's a cupcake.
我们要上路了
We're goin' mobile.
-你叫什么名字  -问这个干吗
- What's your name? - What do you care?
我们在往北开
We're heading north.
听说你...还有几个手下
Heard you had a-- a crew.
你很快就能见到他们了
Well, you'll meet 'em soon enough.
怎么了
What's wrong?
他的声音传输和追踪信号都没了
We've lost his audio and his tracking beacon.
我们在往麦克库克开
We're headin' into McCook.
为什么你一直在说我们的行驶方向
Why do you keep calling out directions?
我和个素昧平生的人坐在一辆车里
I'm in a car with some guy I never met.
他要把我带去一个位置不明的地点
You know, he's taking me to an undisclosed location.
我只是说出脑子里想的而已
You know, I'm just thinkin' out loud.
靠边停
Pull over.
把手机给我
Give me your phone.
我没戴窃听器
I'm not wired.
快点
Do it.
敢开门  你就没命了
Open the door, and you die.
你这简直是胡来
This is so, so dumb.
走吧
Okay.
你好好记住路上的英里标牌
I want you to look at the mile marker and make a note.
-干什么  -等我们交易完
- Why's that? - Once the deal is done,
你得把我带回这里  我好来找手机
you're gonna bring me back here so I can look for that phone.
追踪精度有多少  吉恩
How closely can you track him, Jin?
六米
Six meters.
五米五  差不多吧
Yards, whatever.
先看看钱
Let's see the money.
我这里有两万五
25 large.
另一半在我同伴身上
I left the other half with my associate.
你真以为我会自己带着所有钱来吗
You really think I'll come alone with all the cash?
我们看看枪吧
Well, let's see the damn guns.
看看这些
Look at that.
简直是圣诞节早晨啊
It's just like Christmas morning.
有警察
Cops.
警察
Police!
走
Move!
把枪放下
Put the gun down!
我会开枪的  我发誓
I will drop you, I swear to God.
把枪放下
Put it down.
趴在地上  手心朝上
Get on the ground. Put your palms in the air.
趴下
Get down.
伯吉斯  阿特沃特  有两名白人男性罪犯
Burgess, Atwater, you got two white male offenders
在向你们所在的大楼西南角方向移动
moving southwest of the building towards you.
你还好吗
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
无线电在我的皮带扣里  聪明蛋
The radio was in my belt buckle, slick.
看到了吗
See?
以防你要在牢里跟其他
Just so when you're in gen pop
犯人们讲故事
telling your story,
得把细节都说清楚
you get your details straight.
行动挺迅速的啊
Well, that got crazy fast.
我说了他是个怂货吧
Didn't I tell you he was a cupcake?
我得去处理点别的事
I gotta take care of something.
不要这样
Don't say that.
跟贾斯汀说我突然有事
Tell Justin something popped up.
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
帮我这个忙  好吗
Just do this for me, okay?
-谢谢  -不行
- Thank you. - No.
你是告诉我你现在要去处理的事
You're telling me that whatever you have going on
比去接你的独生儿子
is more important than seeing your only son
-出狱更重要吗  -是的
- walk out of the gates? - Yes.
告诉贾斯汀我爱他  明天会见他的
Tell Justin I love him and I'll see him tomorrow.
你都喝了三杯了
That's your third.
再喝一杯都不成问题  否则今晚不好熬啊
Still one short of getting me through this evening.
贾斯敏
Jasmine.
你搞什么
What the hell?
我妻子想见见你
My wife wanted to meet you.
你怎么不早说
So why didn't you say something?
说了你就不会来了
You would never have come.
是的
You're right.
这是贾斯敏  劳拉
Jasmine, Laura.
这是劳拉  贾斯敏
Laura, Jasmine.
很高兴终于见到你了
Hi. It's--it's nice to finally meet you.
道森太太  我明白的
Look, Mrs. Dawson, I get it, okay?
没人会希望自己的丈夫跟...
Nobody wants their husband to hang out with someone like--
我这样的人在一起  但你要知道
like me, but you know what?
我跟你说明白
Let me tell you something, okay?
我对他没想法  他对我也没有
I got no designs on him, and he's got none on me,
所以既然我们已经说开了...
so if we're done with this little face-to-face...
等等  稍等一下
Wait. Just wait.
我想把这个送给你
I wanted to give you this.
公元四世纪土耳其的一位主教
还是位富有的慈善家  圣诞老人的原型
这是圣·尼古拉斯像
It's, uh, it's St. Nicholas,
孩子的守护神
the patron saint of children.
你帮忙救了我们儿子的命
You helped save our son's life.
我只是想亲自感谢你
I just wanted to thank you personally.
你为什么不告诉我你想见她是因为这个
Why didn't you tell me this is why you wanted to see her?
那样你就不会叫她来了
'Cause you wouldn't have brought her.
从没有谁的妻子感谢过我
Nobody's wife has ever thanked me before.
来吧
Come on.
过来坐
Sit down.
晚上好  女士们
Good evening, ladies.
你要是敢拍照发到网上
You take one photo and post this on facebook,
我就灭了你
I will destroy you.
-收到  -很好
- Copy that. - Good.
我们出发吧
All right, let's do this.
玩得愉快
Have a good night.
好的  谢谢你的电话
All right, well, I appreciate the phone call.
宝贝
Hey, baby.
是谁的电话
Who's on the phone?
那是...
Uh, that was, um...
亚当
Adam.
听着  我想
All right, look, listen, I wanted
告诉你件事  好吗
to bring you in on somethin', okay?
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
他们把我从学院调出来
Um, they didn't pull me out of the academy
不是做文书工作
to do paperwork.
他们把我调出来进情报组了
They pulled me out to work in intelligence.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是好事  对吧
It's a good thing, isn't it?
是啊  天大的好事
Yeah, like you wouldn't believe.
简直太棒了
It's awesome.
有些都工作了十年的人
There's guys with 10 years on the job
还在拼了老命努力
that are still trying to give their left nut
加入这个组
to be in this unit.
那刚才的电话是怎么回事
Well, what was the phone call?
昨天我遇到了一起枪击事件
I was in a shooting yesterday.
什么
What?
-没事的  -天呐  发生了什么事
- It's all right. - Oh my God, what happened?
我打中了
Well, the guy that I shot
想要杀我的人
who was trying to kill me.
他死了  刚才是医院来的电话
He died, and that was the hospital.
你是在逗我玩吗
Are you messin' with me right now?
没有  我没逗你
No. I'm not messing with you.
我只是想告诉你
I just wanted to tell you
以防我今天晚上会心不在焉
in case I'm a little distracted tonight,
但是我不会的
which I won't be,
因为我完全没事
because I'm totally fine, okay?
看看我
Hey, look at me.
什么事都没有
I'm fine. It's all fine.
快来给我长长脸吧
Now, come make me look pretty.
-我们去玩吧  -亚当
- Let's go mingle. - Adam.
你怎么可能没事
How can you be fine?
我不知道  但我确实没事
I don't know. I just am.
好吧
All right.
反正我需要喝一杯
Well, listen, I need a drink.
自由万岁
Freedom!
先生们  很高兴认识你们
Gentlemen, it's been nice.
见到你真高兴  贾斯汀
It's good to see you, Justin.
-你看起来不错啊  -得了吧
- Damn, you are lookin' good. - Get outta here.
现在你看见头山羊都会觉得不错
A goat would look good to you right now.
是啊  可能吧
Yeah, maybe.
我老爹呢
So where's my old man?
他有事情要处理
He had to take care of something.
为什么我一点都不惊讶
Why am I not surprised by that?
别这样  他在工作
Come on, he's working.
是  他永远在工作
Yeah, he's always working.
反正我不在乎
Whatever, I don't care.
我本来就是想见你
I just wanted to see you anyways.
好了  咱们去给你弄点好吃的
All right. Let's go get you a hot meal--
你这是干什么
Whoa, what the hell was that?
我已经不是那个流鼻涕的小屁孩了
Hey, I'm not that snot-nosed kid anymore.
我会证明给你看的  好吗
I'll prove it to you, okay?
来吧  走吧
Come on. Let's go.
你开车还是我开车
You want me to drive, or do you want to drive?
上车吧
Get in the car.
我们什么时候能抓住莫里斯
When are we taking Maurice down?
让我换个说法
Let me rephrase that.
我们必须抓住莫里斯
We need to take Maurice down.
我会的
I will.
最多两星期
Two weeks max.
从今天算起两星期
Two weeks from today?
Two weeks from today.
想得美  钱呢
Nice try. Where is the money?
莫里斯一周给你五千块  哪去了
Maurice gives you 5,000 a week. Where is it?
他没那么多
He didn't have it.
这就怪了
That's funny
我的内线说他存下钱了
'cause my intel said he's stacked.
或许你该在这里见你的内线而不是我
Maybe you should be meeting your intel here and not me.
汉克
Hank.
如果我发现你对我撒谎
If I find out you're lying to me,
我会灭了你的
I will bury you.
你会没事的  伙计
You're gonna be all right, partner.
我只是  我不知道
I just--I don't know.
你怎么知道我不会搞砸
How do you know I won't screw this up
然后她把我赶回来
and she makes me come back?
两个原因
Two reasons.
第一  我知道你是个好孩子
One, because I know you're a good kid,
第二  你知道如果你搞砸了
and two, because you know if you do screw up,
我会千里迢迢去揍你的
I'm driving all the way there to kick your ass.
看看你  都长这么大了
Look at you, all grown up.
莎纳阿姨
Hey, Aunt Shona.
-汉克·博伊特  -莎纳·威廉姆斯
- Hank Voight. - Shona Williams.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
这个  用来顶些开销
Here, to help cover costs.
这我不能拿
I can't take this.
相信我  等德安东尼
Delieve me, by the time D'anthony
恢复了胃口
gets his appetite back,
这连他的早饭都不够
that will barely cover breakfast.
你真是好人
That's very nice of you.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你
客气了
Any time.